Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - Whe (Box 281)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 281)
    - 1921-1933 (Box 281)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 281)
  - Whi-Why (Box 281)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 281)
    - 1916-1919 (Box 281)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 281)
  - Whi-Why, 1921-1923 (Box 281)
  - Whisenard, Mrs. J.W., 1914-1915 (Box 281)
  - Whit (Box 281)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 281)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 281)
  - Whit (Box 282)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 282)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 282)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 282)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 282)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 282)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 282)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 282)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 282)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 282)
  - White (Box 282)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 282)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 282)
  - White, Evelyn Marshall, 1932-1937 (Box 282)
  - White, Dr. Jesse H., 1934-1935 (Box 282)
  - White, R. Clyde (Box 282)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 282)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 282)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 282)
  - White, R. Clyde (Box 283)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 283)
  - Whitehead & Woag Company, 1913-1914 (Box 283)
  - Whiti, 1923-1937 (Box 283)
  - Whiting Paper Company, 1914-1916 (Box 283)
  - Wi (Box 283)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 283)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 283)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 283)
  - Wia-Wie, 1913-1923 (Box 283)
  - Wia-Wil, 1928-1929 (Box 283)
  - Wie, 1924-1936 (Box 283)
  - Wif-Wik, 1913-1922 (Box 283)
  - Wil (Box 283)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 283)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 283)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 283)
    - 1931-1935 (Box 283)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 283)
  - Wila-Wilk (Box 283)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 283)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 283)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 283)
  - Wildermuth, Ora L. (Box 283)
    - 1924-1928 (Box 283)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 283)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 283)
  - Wildermuth, Ora L. (Box 284)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 284)
    - Building matters, 1934-1935 (Box 284)
    - September 1935-April 1936 (Box 284)
    - May-September 1936 (Box 284)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 284)
  - Wilh, 1923-1937 (Box 284)
  - Will (Box 284)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 284)
    - 1916-1918 (Box 284)
    - 1918-1920 (Box 284)
    - 1920-1922 (Box 284)
    - 1922-1925 (Box 284)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 284)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 284)
  - Willbern, Glen D., 1929-1937 (Box 284)
  - Willi (Box 284)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 284)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 284)
  - Willi (Box 285)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 285)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 285)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 285)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 285)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 285)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 285)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 285)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 285)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 285)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 285)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 285)
  - Williams, Edith, 1918 (Box 285)
  - Williams, O.H., 1914-1924 (Box 285)
  - Williams, Kenneth P. (Box 285)
    - 1913-1936 (Box 285)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 285)
  - Williford, E. Allan, October 1915 (Box 285)
  - Wilm-Wilz, 1913-1924 (Box 285)
  - Wils, 1923-1924 (Box 285)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 285)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 285)
  - Wils (Box 286)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 286)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 286)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 286)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 286)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 286)
  - Wilson (Box 286)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 286)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 286)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 286)
  - Wim-Wip (Box 286)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 286)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 286)
  - Wim-Wn, 1928-1929 (Box 286)
  - Win (Box 286)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 286)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 286)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 286)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 286)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 286)
  - Wing, Charles, 1922 (Box 286)
  - Winona College, 1913-1919 (Box 286)
  - Wins, 1923-1937 (Box 287)
  - Winther, Oscar, 1936 (Box 287)
  - Wir-Wiz (Box 287)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 287)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 287)
  - Wis (Box 287)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 287)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 287)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 287)
  - Wisconsin, University of (Box 287)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 287)
    - 1916-1921 (Box 287)
    - 1921-1924 (Box 287)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 287)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 287)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 287)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 287)
  - Wit (Box 287)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 287)
  - Wit (Box 288)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 288)
  - Wo (Box 288)
    - 1923-1932 (Box 288)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 288)
  - Wo-Wz, 1928-1929 (Box 288)
  - Woa-Wok, 1913-1923 (Box 288)
  - Wol, 1923-1937 (Box 288)
  - Wol-Won (Box 288)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 288)
    - 1916-1921 (Box 288)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 288)
  - Woldenberg & Schaar, 1913-1916 (Box 288)
  - Wolfe (Box 288)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 288)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 288)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 288)
  - Women, Dean of—Trustees' reports (Box 288)
    - 1914-1916 (Box 288)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 288)
  - Women's dormitory, 1924-1925 (Box 288)
  - Women's dormitory (Box 288)
    - Correspondence with contractors, etc., 1935-1937 (Box 288)
    - First filing of bids, letters, etc., 1924-1925 (Box 288)
    - New one, 1935 (Box 288)
    - Reports of work, 1925 (Box 288)
  - Women's League, 1915-1918 (Box 288)
  - Women's Pan-Hellenic Council, c.1937 (Box 288)
  - Women—PhD's, 1908-1928 (Box 288)
  - Women's Self-Government Association, 1923-1927 (Box 288)
  - Women's War Service (WWI), undated (Box 288)
  - Woo (Box 288)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 288)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 288)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 288)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 288)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 288)
  - Woo (Box 289)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 289)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 289)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 289)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 289)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 289)
  - Woo-Wop (Box 289)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 289)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 289)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 289)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 289)
  - Wood, 1929-1930 (Box 289)
  - Woodbridge, Lydia D., 1919-1937 (Box 289)
  - Woodburn, James A. (Box 289)
    - 1914 (Box 289)
    - 1914-1919 (Box 289)
    - 1919-1922 (Box 289)
    - 1922-1925 (Box 289)
    - 1925-1932 (Box 289)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 289)
  - Woodl, 1936 (Box 289)
  - Wor (Box 289)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 289)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 289)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 289)
  - Wor (Box 290)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 290)
  - Wor-Woz, 1913-1923 (Box 290)
  - Works Progress Administration (Box 290)
    - General, 1935-1937 (Box 290)
    - Walks, drives, grading projects on campus, 1936-1937 (Box 290)
  - World's Fair, 1931-1933 (Box 290)
  - Wr (Box 290)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 290)
    - 1918-1922 (Box 290)
    - 1922-1927 (Box 290)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 290)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 290)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 290)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 290)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 290)
  - Wreidt, E.A.—State Vocational Director, 1921 (Box 290)
  - Wright, William P., 1932-1933 (Box 290)
  - Wu, 1923-1927 (Box 290)
  - Wu-Wy (Box 290)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 290)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 290)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 290)
  - Wy (Box 290)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 290)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 290)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 290)
  - Wyoming, University of, 1915-1918 (Box 291)
  - X-Y (Box 291)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 291)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 291)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 291)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 291)
  - X-Y (Box 291)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 291)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 291)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 291)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 291)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 291)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 291)
  - X-Ray, 1929 (Box 291)
  - Yale University (Box 291)
    - 1913-1925 (Box 291)
    - 1925-1931 (Box 291)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 291)
  - Yellen, Samuel, 1929-1937 (Box 291)
  - Y.M.C.A. (Box 291)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 291)
    - 1917-1921 (Box 291)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 291)
  - Y.M.C.A. (Box 292)
    - 1925-1937 (Box 292)
    - Indiana University (Box 292)
      - 1913-1919 (Box 292)
      - 1919-1925 (Box 292)
      - 1925-1932 (Box 292)
      - 1932-1937 (Box 292)
  - Yo (Box 292)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 292)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 292)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 292)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 292)
  - Yo (Box 292)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 292)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 292)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 292)
  - Young, Bert E. (Box 292)
    (Department of Romance Languages / Department of French and Italian)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 292)
  - Young, Bert E. (Box 293)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 293)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 293)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 293)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 293)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 293)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 293)
  - Young, Chan-Sain, 1928-1929 (Box 293)
  - Young, Mrs. Grace P., 1923-1924 (Box 293)
  - Y.W.C.A. (Box 293)
    - 1913-1933 (Box 293)
    - Indiana University, 1914-1937 (Box 293)
  - Z (Box 293)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 293)
    - 1917-1921 (Box 293)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 293)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 293)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 293)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 293)
  - Zeuch, William Edward, 1917 (Box 293)
  - Zi (Box 293)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 293)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 293)
  - Ziemer, Gregor, 1935-1936 (Box 293)
  - Zim (Box 293)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 293)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 293)
  - Zo, 1925-1926 (Box 293)
  - Zucker, Adolf, 1936-1937 (Box 293)